Aditi Parikh

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Profile

I'm not your average MERN stack developer. With a background in sales and marketing, I bring a fresh perspective and a unique set of skills to the table. I've got a year of experience under my belt and am ready to take my skills to the next level as a junior-level developer. I'm a pro at MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, and Node.js, and I've got a flair for creating stunning web apps and RESTful APIs. I'm passionate about delivering top-notch code and staying ahead of the curve with the latest tech trends. Let's team up and create some truly amazing projects!

Projects

Recipe Diary

This is a RESTful web-app providing recipe management for users. With CRUD endpoints to recipes, along with user authentication and personalised dashboard, managing your favorite recipes in one place has made it more convenient. Repo Link

Skills: React.js, Express.js, Node.js and MongoDB Atlas

SayIt

Created an anonymous forums for users to express their thoughts. The functionality had likes, react via emoticons and comment features such that users can interact with posts. Repo Link

Skills: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Express.js and MongoDB.

Juggenaut Bistro

Sprouted from my idea of having a fusion bistro for Indian street-food and the UK cafe culture. The logo and design have come from the same fundamental idea, created using Photoshop and images are used from a stock source. Repo Link

Skills: HTML, CSS, Javascript and PostgreSQL.

Voyage

A website created from my hobby of travelling. This is my current running project encompassing user registration, wish-list destinations on dashboard and search ability for locations with a response of key facts and things-to-do. Repo Link

Skills: React.js, Express.js, Node.js, PostreSQL

Courses

Full Stack Software Developer, FutureProof

JULY 2022 - SEPTEMBER 2022

The Complete 2022 Web Developer Bootcamp, Udemy

APRIL 2021 - MARCH 2022

Details

15 Roke Lodge Road, Kenley CR8 5NA, London United Kingdom 07897606428 aditi.parikh0526@gmail.com

Skills

HTML & CSS + Tailwind

JavaScript ES6

Node.js

Express.js

React.js + Redux

Vue.js

MongoDB

SQL

Git and GitHub

PHP

Data Structures and Algorithms

Microsoft Office Suite

Links

GitHub Projects

LinkedIn

Languages

English

Hindi

Internships

Web Developer, 3W Creators LLP, Vadodara, India

NOVEMBER 2021 - MARCH 2022

- Applied my on-going learning within development to actual webdevelopment projects.
- Completed 3 full web front-ends.
- Responsible for creating and updating wireframe designs from communication with clients.
- Created responsive and functional UI using CSS Flexbox to allow viewers to access web pages irrespective of the resolution.
- Worked closely with senior developers, designers and copywriters to create complete website front-ends.

Employment History

Head Counsellor, Gujarat University, Ahmedabad, India

MAY 2018 - MARCH 2021

- To assist and counsel the students regarding their post graduation academics and future learning routes such as Cyber Security.
- To connect, arrange interviews and manage placements for the students and conducted over 50 workshops with 85% employment turnover rate.
- Researched and presented upcoming technologies to board members for inclusion in courses that increased course enlisting by 60%.

Sales Manager, Abellon Clean Energy, Ahmedabad, India

NOVEMBER 2017 - MAY 2018

- Attending and understanding sales inquiries and requirements, preparing quotation and proposals to clients.
- Monitored team performance, identified shortcomings and proposed improvements that boosted KPIs by 25%. Managed and maintained documentation related to RFIs, RFQs and proposals.
- Prepared and archived regular MIS reports for solar divisional products.

Education

BSc Hospitality Management, MS University, Vadodara, India

SEPTEMBER 2011 - SEPTEMBER 2014